People in the United States who are struggling to survive, who are having their black and brown babies chased and killed by police officers or kidnapped by ICE, people who are facing homelessness, those who are having to choose whether to pay medical bills, student loans, or rent, people who are overworked and underpaid do not need any foreign government or entity to tell them that this capitalist system is killing us.
We feel it in our bones and we feel it in our bodies every day.
The Trump administration is persecuting people and organizations for promoting critical thought, for raising questions, and exposing the very criminal nature of this administration and the billionaires that it serves.
On July 20th, the State Department released Cuba, the capital of 21st century communism, a report that is both ridiculous and dangerous.
Its vagueness is the point.
It doesn't share any real or clear definition of the threat, which means anyone can be targeted.
And this is political warfare.
It's a clear warning.
You stand behind the racist attacks against immigrants and black communities.
You support and cheer on the wars, the genocide, the blockades, or you are a communist, an enemy of the state.
On July 24th, the House Ways and Means Committee issued subpoenas to the People's Forum, an educational and cultural organization advocating for the transformation of this ruthless system.
They've subpoenaed Breakthrough News, an independent media outlet uplifting people's struggles from across the world, and Tri-Continental Institute for Social Research, a research institute that serves the people.
This is a witch hunt, and no one, no one is safe.
So let's be clear.
They use Cuba to build a dangerous narrative, but these attacks on Cuba aren't only about Cuba and the continued genocidal policy against the Cuban people.
They're about dismantling movements right here at home.
They want to destroy organizations fighting for workers, for women, for trans people, for immigrants, and against the attacks on black America.
Why? Because they are terrified.
People are fed up, and people are organizing across struggles.
And we have to be clear, this is not a time to let fear consume us.
This is a time for clarity, for denunciation, and collective struggle.
History, not far from us or far away lands, but right here, show us that an authoritarian government who fears people power,
start by attacking communists and radicals, but they always come for everyone.
So no one is safe.
When it comes to Cuba, we have to remain steadfast in our humanity.
You don't have to be a socialist or a communist to oppose the U.S. blockade on Cuba and feel moved to show solidarity.
You just have to be a decent human being.
No conscious person enjoys knowing that 11 million people are living in the dark because the wealthiest country in the world,
the United States, has decided that this is the fate of other human beings.
100,000 people, 12,000 of them, children waiting for surgeries because one nation decided on collective punishment
because they consider Cuba's political ideology a threat.
Cuba does not need charity.
Cuba needs an end to the blockade.
Cuba is not a threat.
The U.S. blockade on Cuba is a threat to human life.
Please remember the Red Scare crushed movements, and it resulted in fearful conformity,
a vacuum of independent organizations of our people.
We cannot allow for this to happen again.
We have advanced too much in our struggles.
We won't be dragged back.
We will not be demobilized.
We will not be silenced.
Solidarity is not a crime.
It is our duty.
The people organizing, mobilizing, and demanding what we rightfully deserve
and advancing our struggles against capitalism is not a crime.
It is our right.
So keep solidarity, keep mobilizing, keep organizing, and keep defending our very right to free speech.
We will not be silenced.